剧情回顾...
你把我带来是给你做手术的
You brought me here to operate on you.
你认为我相信你 我就...
You think, I trust you,that I am gonna just...
做完手术你就让我走人?
do the surgery and hope that you let me go?
你必须得做
You have to do it.
-他们是怎么让你来求我的?  -Jack 别这样...
-How did they get you to ask me?  -Please...
-他们给你什么好处?  -什么都没有
-What did they offer you?  -Nothing.
-那你来这儿干什么?  -他们要杀了 Sawyer...
-Then what are you doing here?  -They're gonna kill Sawyer...
明天早上 首先
Tomorrow morning, first thing,
会帮你去处肿瘤 让你活下去
we'll get it out,and they'll keep you alive.
我准备好了
I'm ready.
Sawyer 求你了!
Sawyer, please!
别碰他!
You get your hands off of him!
我刚在Ben的肾脏旁边切了一个口
I just made a small incision in Ben's kidney sac.
如果我一小时内不帮他缝上 他就会死
Now if I don't stitch that back up in the next hour, he's dead.
把对讲机拿进来
Now get in here,and bring that walkie-talkie.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
仅供学习交流之用 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎访问YYeTs美剧论坛进行交流 www.YYETS.com
■
翻译： 小黄  后期：梁良 双语字幕：sealovemoon
我刚才睡着了
I fell asleep.
那很安全的
With candles burning..that's real safe.
我们不用一直这样做的
We don't have to keep doing this,you know.
你这样说是因为你觉得这些没用吗?
Are you saying that because you don't think it's gonna work
还是害怕他会发现这一切?
or because you're afraid he'll find out?
把上衣拉起来
Lift up your shirt.
医生都像你这样
Some doctor you are.
我这样做不是因为我是医生
I'm not doing this as your doctor.
而是因为我是你姐姐
I'm doing it as your sister.
我不希望你单独在这儿
I don't like you being here alone.
搬来和我一起住吧
Come stay with me.
我喜欢住在海滩上
I like living on the beach.
这是迈阿密 Rachel
This is Miami, Rachel.
一切都在海滩上
Everything's on the beach.
你们有大约一个小时的时间逃走 他们不会去追你
You have about an hour head start before they come after you.
带上对讲机 带上 Sawyer 跑
Take the walkie, take Sawyer and go.
等等  你在哪儿?你在哪?
Wait. Where are you?
Kate 听我说
Kate, listen to me. Just listen to me.
记得我在海滩上和你说的话吗?
You remember what I told you on the beach?
我讲给你的故事 当你帮我缝针的时候?
Do you rember what story I told you when you were stitching me up?
你记得吗?!
Do you rember it?!
是的  我记得!
Yes, yes, I remember!
当你安全了 你用对讲机给我讲那个故事
When you get safe, you radio me and you tell me that story.
Jack 求你了...
Jack, please...
如果一小时后我听不到你的声音
If I don't get a call from you in the next hour,
我就知道事情不对 他死定了!
I'm gonna know something went wrong,and he dies!
我不能抛下你不管
I can't leave without you.
不  你要这样做
Yes, you are. Go.
-Jack 我不能!  -现在就跑
-Jack, I can't!  -Go, now.
我做不到!
I can't!
Kate 不要说了 快跑!
Kate, damn it, run!
Juliet 为他止血 帮他缝合
Juliet, stop the bleeding and stitch him up.
她不是外科医生
She's not a surgeon.
所以她办不到
She can't fix this.
他是对的
He's right.
我们快跑
Let's go.
警报!警报!
Warning.
Sawyer 快跑!
Sawyer, let's go!
那你有什么好的建议?
Then what the hell do you suggest we do?
找到 Danny
Go get Danny,
还有 Austen 和 Ford 然后把他们带回来
then find Austen and Ford and bring them back.
-如果你这样做 Ben 就死定了  -快去
-No, you do that, and Ben dies.  -Go.
你认为我是在开玩笑吗?
You think I'm lying?Do you think this is a bluff?
-我说到做到!  -Jack 你不会的
-I will let him die!  -No, Jack, you won't.
去带他们回来
Go. Get them back.
如果必要的话...
If you have to...
杀了他们
kill them.
-Burke 医生  -是的
-Dr. Burke?  -Yes.
我是 Mittelos 生物实验室的 Diana
This is Diana from Mittelos Bioscience.
我是来确认明天你的预约
I'm calling to confirm your appointment tomorrow.
啊 2点 对吗?
Uh, 2:00, right?
是2点 Alpert 医生让我告诉你
2:00. Dr. Alpert asked me to tell you
他很期待和你的见面
that he's very much looking forward to meeting you.
我也是 谢谢你
Me, too. Thank you.
再见
Good-Bye.
待在这
Stay here.
你好 Juliet
Hello, Juliet.
你到底在这干什么?
Why exactly are you here?
哦 我...
Oh, I, m...
今天的实验室工作...
today's lab work...
回到家我发现自己算错了些数字
I got home, and I realized that inverted some numbers.
难道不能等到明天吗?
And it couldn't wait till the morning?
恩... Edmund?
Um... Edmund?
不好意思
I'm sorry.
看我都忘了介绍了
How rude of me.
呃 Juliet  这是 Sherry
Uh, Juliet, this is Sherry.
Sherry  这是 Juliet
Sherry, this is Juliet,
我的前妻
My ex-wife.
Juliet 现在就走
Juliet's leaving.
是的
I am.
你能把灯关了吗?
Could you please turn off the lights?
你还是想不通吗? Jack
You haven't thought this through, Jack.
你的计划行不通的
Your plan's not gonna work.
是吗? 为什么?
Yeah? Why is that?
你的朋友回不到你们那边的岛上
Your friends aren't going to make it back to your side
因为我们在另一座岛上
of the island because we're not on that island.
我们在两公里远的另一个更小的岛上
We're on a smaller island 2 miles offshore.
恐怕是这样
'Fraid so.
那么我们为什么不讨论下
So why don't we see if we can come up
和平的解决方案?
with some kind of peaceful resolution?
和平的方案?
A peaceful resolution?
是的
That's right.
这就是你所谓的 让我杀死 Ben
Is that what you call asking me to kill Ben
在手术台上...
while on the operang table...
-让别人以为是医疗事故?  -那真是荒唐
-Make it look like an accident?  -That's ridiculous.
-她想让 Ben 去死  -他在撒谎
-She wants Ben to die.  -He's lying.
她承诺我如果我这样做的话...她会保护我的
She said if I did it,that she would protect me...
够了!
Enough!
滚出去
Get out.
Tom 他说的不是真的
Tom, he's lying.
你说你不能帮他缝合...
You said you can't stitch him up...
那你就没必要留在这儿
then you don't need to be in here.
去吧 Julie.
Go, Julie.
别让他把你给耍了
Don't let him fool you.
他绝对不会让一个病人这样去死的
He'll never let a patient just die.
有人听见我吗?!
Can anybody hear me?!
怎么了?
What happened?
打开笼子
Open the cage.
打开这该死的笼子
Just open the damn cage!
那是我们那个岛吗?
That's our island?
你不相信我告诉你的?
What, you didn't believe me when I told you before?
我们需要一艘船
We need a boat.
是啊 几块餐巾和自助餐吗?
Yeah, a couple of towels and a buffet lunch.
我们沿着海滩走
We'll keep following the beach.
这儿一定会有一条船
There's gotta be one around here somewhere.
否则他们是怎么往返的?
How else do they get back and forth?
你为什么不停下? 问一下我们的方位?
Why don't we just stop and ask for directions?
Jack 你在吗?
Jack, are you there?
-是的  -你还好吗?
-Yeah, I'm here.  -Are you okay?
-我很好  -怎么不帮我向他打招呼?
-I'm fine.  -Tell him I said "hi"?
-切入主题啊!  -Jack 我们需要一条船
-Get to the point!  -We need a boat.
我们要想办法离开这个岛
We need some way to get off of this island.
你听见了?
You heard her.
他们怎么才能离开这?!
How do they get off this island?!
他在干吗?
What's he doing?
快追!
Come on!
这边走!
This way!
Jason 你还好吗?
Jason, you all right?
在那边 在那边!
Over there! There!
快点钻进去!
Come on! Get inside, get inside! Go!
快!
Come on!
轻点 轻点!
Be quiet, be quiet, be quiet.
怎么了?
What?
他们朝哪里跑了?
Where'd they go?
那边
That way.
很高兴见到你 Sheena
Nice to meet you, Sheena.
那是真的吗?
Is it true?
你指什么?
Is what true?
你刚才说的...
What you said...
Juliet 真的让你杀了他吗?
Did Juliet really ask you to kill him?
当然...
Yeah...
还有大约40分钟 她的愿望就要实现了
and in about 40 minutes,she's gonna get her wish.
这样... 没有... 任何帮助...
That's... not... helping...
所有一切
anything.
现在...
Now...
谁能帮我找到 Juliet?
could somebody please get Juliet?
Juliet  Edmund 想和你谈谈
Edmund wants to see you in his office.
你是这里的员工?
Do you work here?
我是新来的助理
I'm the new research assistant.
当然
Of course you are.
我要你说出真相
I want in.
什么真相
In on what?
我知道你在做什么 Juliet
I know what you're doing, Juliet.
我真的不知道...
I'm not really sure what...
我读了你的笔记
I read your notes.
我知道你从实验室拿了什么
I know what you took from the lab.
我唯一不知道的是...
The only thing I don't know is...
你是在帮谁?
who's your guinea pig?
Ed 我...
Ed, I've...
我只是在做我自己的工作
I've been doing my research in my own lab, on my own time.
-我真的不知道..  -是你妹妹 不是吗?
-I don't really see..  -It's your sister, isn't it?
Jules 你有两条路可走...
Look, Jules,there's two ways this plays out...
一条是 你的研究大有前途
One is, your research is potentially genius.
另一条是
And the other,
你有伦理道德上的问题
you're raising some very serious ethical questions,
也许甚至触发犯罪...
maybe even criminal concerns...
但要是你和我合作的话
but if you collaborate with me,
基于我的名誉
based on my reputation,
我们将突破科学的边缘
all this is viewed as cutting edge science.
然后为成就举杯庆祝
And we will win prizes and drink Champagne
这样能为人类做出贡献
and do a lot of good for people.
我给你一些时间想想清楚
Why don't I give you some time to think about it?
Ben 醒了
Ben's awake.
怎么可能?
How?
Shephard 说他是脊柱外科医生 不是麻醉师
Shephard says he's a spinal surgeon,not an anesthesiologist.
Ben 要你去
Ben's asking for you.
你的兴趣就是挖洞吗?
This a hobby of yours, underdog,digging holes?
是的 还有织网
Yep, that and basket weaving.
你指哪样?
Want one?
那这里有没有一个通向大陆的通道?
Happen to have a tunnel to the mainland?
没有 但我有条船
No, but I've got a boat.
我们能用它吗?
Can we use it?
是的 但我们得赶快
Yeah, but we've got to hurry.
等等 小妞
Hold on a second, sister.
你就这样碰巧在丛林里找到我们 又碰巧有条船?
You just happen to find us in the woods,you just happen to have a boat,
还帮我们逃走?
and you're gonna let us use it, huh?
我们得先办件事
There's something we need to do first.
哦 天...
Oh, gee...
我的男友被关起来了
My boyfriend is being held prisoner.
如果你们帮我救他 我保证
If you help me rescue him,I promise you,
把你们带回到你们来的地方
I'll get you back to the other island.
你男朋友..他的名字不会是 Karl 吧?
Your boyfriend..his name happen to be Karl?
是的
Yeah.
好吧 快走
Ah, come on.
我停止了手术
I stopped the surgery.
我知道
I know.
我隐约听见了些东西
I've been able to hear you for a few minutes now.
你真聪明
It's very clever of you.
我应该料到的
I should have seen it coming.
你很疼吗?
Are you in pain?
-我可以... -不
-I can...-No.
但还是谢谢
But thanks all the same.
我希望和 Juliet 单独谈谈 求你了 Jack
I'd like to speak to Juliet alone,please, Jack.
抱歉 这样不行
No, I'm sorry.
求你了 这是一个绅士的请求
Please, I'm asking you...one gentleman to another.
就给我3分钟
It won't hurt you to give me 3 minutes,
好吗...
will it...
知道我还有27分钟可活?
Knowing I have only 27 left?
如果你碰他
If you touch him,
-如果你想要...  -我不会的
-if you try to...  -I won't.
你只有3分钟
You've got three minutes.
我的名字是 Tom
I'm Tom, by the way.
他们有过一段历史
They've got history.
我希望你能进去
I would like for you to go back in there,
完成他的手术
put Ben under and finish the surgery.
我为什么要这样做?
And why would I want to do that?
我能帮你的朋友逃跑
Because I'm going to go help your friends escape.
非常感谢你给我们时间挑选 Dr. Burke.
Thank you for taking the time to let us make our pitch, Dr. Burke.
Mittelos 生物学工程的基地在俄勒冈
Mittelos Bioscience is based in Oregon.
我们的在波特兰的边上
We're just outside of Portland.
这张照片看上去有点 uh cheeseball
These shots might seem a little,uh, cheeseball,
但我们的确很高兴
but our people really are this happy.
因为我们是私营基金
Now why? Because we're privately funded.
那意味这自由
Privately funded means freedom.
我们每星期组织游历波特兰的活动
We organize trips every week in and around the Portland area,
是些徒步 单车 和水上活动
which is just awesome for hiking and biking and river running.
但你...
Look, when you...
你们公司找到我时 我真是受宠若惊
your company reached out to me,I was flattered,
但我真的不知道为什么你要...
but I don't really know why you would want me to...
你使一只雄性老鼠受精 这是真的吗?
Is it true that you successfully impregnated a male field mouse?
这项研究是没有期限的
It didn't carry to term.
我能问你些事吗?
Mind if I ask you something?
当然
Sure.
你看到了什么?
What do you see?
显然是人的子宫
It's a human womb, obviously.
根据这张图像
Judging from the decomposition of the endometrium,
这个子宫属于一个70多岁的老人
I would say that the woman was somewhere in her 70s.
不 实际上 她才26岁
No, actually, she's 26.
怎么可能?
What happened to her?
要是我告诉你你能用 所有的资金去找到答案怎么样?
What if I told you that you could have complete freedom and money to find out?
我们认为你很特别 Burke医生
We think you're special, Dr. Burke,
我们需要你带领这个团队
and we want you to lead a team
或者是训练有素的人员 因为我知道你很出色
of highly trained people because we think you're just that good.
我不能
I can't.
为什么?
Why can't you?
我前夫不会让我这样做的 我...
My ex-husband wouldn't let me. I...
他不想让你得到这个机会?
He wouldn't want you to have this opportunity?
他什么也不想让我得到
He doesn't want me to have anything.He would never give the okay.
我们能和他联系吗?
Maybe we could reach out to him
-以你的名义...  -不用麻烦了
-on your behalf...  -Don't bother.
他总得有所反应
There must be something that he would respond to.
如果他被汽车撞了如何?
If he were hit by a bus..How about that? That would work.
这样说太不合适了
That was totally inappropriate.
不  不...不  我...
No, no...No, I, uh...
很抱歉浪费了你的时间
I'm sorry that I wasted your time.
-Burke医生 求你...  -不行 抱歉
-Dr. Burke, please, you...  -No, I'm sorry.
我不是你所想象的那样的人
Whatever you think I am, I'm not.
我不是一个领袖 Alpert先生
I'm not a leader, Mr. Alpert.
我一团糟
I'm a mess.
该死的
Well, hell.
Karl 一定在这里
Karl's gotta be in there.
你还不确定吗?
What, you mean you ain't sure?
这是唯一我没见过的地方
It's the only place I haven't looked.
你认识那个看守?
You know the guard?
是的 他叫 Aldo
Yeah. His name's Aldo.
好了 小妞
Okay, Lollipop,
我们没枪没子弹 怎么才能过他这关?
you wanna tell me how we're gonna get by him with one gun and no bullets?
我有主意了
I've got an idea.
那当然
Of course you do.
把门打开!
Open the door!
Alex? 你在这儿干嘛?
Alex? What the hell are you doing?
他们一定是逃出来了 我在丛林里抓到他们了
They must've gotten out of their cages.I caught them in the jungle.
快把门打开 Aldo!
Now open up, Aldo!
停下! 你不该出现在这里的
Just stop!You're not supposed to be here.
如果你爸知道了 他会杀了我的
If your dad finds out,he's gonna kill me.
是他让我把他们带来你这里的
My dad was the one who told me to bring them here, to you.
哦 也许你可以问问他
Look, maybe you should call him.
我相信他没有更好的办法
I'm sure he's got nothing better to do.
Danny 我要和 Ben 说话
Danny, I need Ben.
干嘛?!
Why?!
听着  Alex在这儿
Listen, I got Alex here.
她抓了 Austen 和 Ford...
She's got Austen and Ford with her...
可恶 别相信她
Damn it, whatever she says,don't believe it.
你守着他们 我...
You hold 'em right there. I'm on my...
不要因为你太蠢就冲我来
Don't get mad at me just 'cause you were dumb enough
你真不是当看守的料
to fall for the old "wookiee prisoner" gag.
Karl 在哪儿?
Where's Karl?
你在说什么 我不知道!
I have no idea what you're talking about.
射他的膝盖
Shoot him in the knee.
-什么?  -把枪给我
-What?  -Give me the rifle.
别浪费时间 让我来
We don't have time for this. I'll do it.
好吧 好吧! 他被关在大厅末端的23号房间
Okay, all right!He's at the end of the hall, room 23.
钥匙在我口袋里
Keys are in my back pocket.
干的好 小妞
Damn good con, Freckles.
我还真以为你会射他
I almost believed you were gonna shoot that boy.
我可是动真格的
It wasn't a con.
在这里!
Here it is!
Sawyer!
帮我!
Help!
过来帮忙!
-他还好吗?  -我们已经救出你的男友了
-Is he okay?  -We got your boyfriend back.
那条该死的船在哪里?
Now where's your damn boat?
蠢货!
Idiot!
-他们在哪?  -我不知道
-Where are they?  -I don't know.
-Alex 和他们在一起  -Danny!
-Alex was with them.  -Danny!
放他们走!
We're letting them go.
-放他们走?  -这是 Ben 下的命令
-Letting them go?  -Ben gave the order.
-Ben 在手术 我刚去过 -他醒了
-Ben's in surgery. I was just there.-He woke up.
-哦 他醒了?  -Shephard 停止了手术
-Oh, he woke up, huh?  -Shephard won't finish the surgery
除非让他的朋友逃走
unless he knows his friends are off the island.
你想让 Ben 死吗?
Do you want Ben to die?
Ben 死也不放他们走的
I know Ben would rather die than let them go.
面试怎么样?
How was the interview?
不怎么好
It's not for me.
-什么?  -没关系的
-What?  -It's fine.
他们在波特兰
They're too far away, anyway.It's Portland.
是因为我你才说不的吧 Jules?
Jules, you didn't say no because of me?
我怎么会大老远的去波特兰
Well, why would I wanna go all the way to Portland
那地方不适合研究
for research that doesn't even work?
因为那能行
Because it does work.
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
我怀...我怀孕了
I'm pre...I'm pregnant.
怎么可能?
What?
看 我有血液测试
Look, look. I took a blood test, too.
我想等确定了才告诉你
I didn't want to tell you until I was sure.
-那行的通的  -是的
-It worked.  -Yeah.
我一生所求就是想要个孩子
All my life, all I've ever wanted was to have a baby,
现在 因为你 我...
and now, because of you, I'm gonna...
天啊 现在我只需要恢复身体
God, now I just need to get healthy.
我只需要...只需要恢复身体
Now I just need...I just need to get healthy
这样能看着我的小家伙 考上常青藤大学
so I can see the little bugger get into an ivy league school, you know?
你会的 你当然会的
You will. Of course you will.
你现在能告诉你那无耻的前夫
Hey, now you can tell that bastard ex-husband of yours
他是怎么认识伦理的?
what he can do with his ethics.
这是因为你不会忍耐 你很刻薄
Because you're insufferable,and you're mean.
妈 你要知道真相 那..
Well, you asked me for the truth, mom,and that's..
我一会儿在打来 好吗?
Let me call you later, okay?
你好 Jules 怎么啦?
Hello, Jules. What's up?
她怀孕了
She's pregnant.
怎么可能?
Excuse me?
成功了 Rachel 怀孕了
It worked. Rachel's pregnant.
Julie 那真是...
Julie, that's...
我需要看下你的研究
I need,I need to see your labs.
要确认下数据..
We'll have to verify the data before..
不行
No.
我对登报不感兴趣 ED
I'm not interested in publishing, Ed.
她是我妹妹
It's my sister.
也好 如果你不感兴趣的话 你为什么关心..
Fine, then if you're not interested,why are you concerned if..
你还好吗?
You okay?
是的
Yeah.
只是对血有点过敏
I just don't like blood too much.
那...
Well...
你一定不愿意看这个
then you probably won't wanna be looking at that.
如果你们真能离开这座岛的话
So,if you really can get off the island,
怎么不把他带到医院去?
why didn't you just take him to a facility?
为什么要这样?
Why all this?
因为自从天空变成紫色 我们..
Because ever since the sky turned purple, we..
到底发生了什么?!
What the hell happened?!
我刚割开了他的动脉
I just nicked an artery.
你刚才不是已经做了吗?!
Isn't that what you already did?!
是的 只不过那次是故意的
Yeah, well, that was on purpose.
能弄好吗?
Can you fix it?
该死的
Damn it.
-你抱住了吗? -行
-You got him?-I got him.
好一次旅行!
Nice ride!
-帮我  -我们必须离开 好吗?
-Help me.  -We gotta go now, okay?
能行吗?
Can you stand?
好了 快点
All right, come on.
你是老大的女儿 是吗?
So... you're the boss' daughter, huh?
没想到啊
Never saw that coming.
我们走 小妞
Let's go, Cheech.
去一次旅行
We're goin' for a little ride.
-小心点  -好 放松
-Careful.  -All right, easy.
我要把你放到船上 好吗?
I'm gonna put you in the boat,all right?
等等!
Wait, wait.
-你会好起来的  -Danny...
-You're gonna be okay.  -Danny...
不 我是Sawyer
No, Sawyer.
Danny!
-怎么了 他..  -我看不见
-What happened? Is he...  -I can't see.
-什么?  -我看不见
-What?  -I can't see.
太多血了
There's too much blood.
过来一下
All right, get over here.
Tom 如果你不过来的话 他会死的
Tom, he's gonna die if you don't get over here right now.
去吧
Go.
离开这儿
Get outta here.
好吧! 听美女的
You heard the lady.
我们走
Let's go.
Alex 你不能
Not you, Alex.
-你得留下  -为什么?
-You're staying.  -Why?
我们都知道你的父亲
We both know your father,
他让 Karl 活着的唯一要求是 你在这儿等他醒来
and the only way he'll let Karl live is if you're here when he wakes up.
我很抱歉 Alex
I'm sorry, Alex.
嘿 Alex
Hey, Alex.
我很想念你
I missed you.
我知道
I know.
我也很想念你
I missed you, too.
现在你必须得走了
You have to go away now,
但我会很快见到你的 好吗?
but I'll see you real soon, okay?
我爱你
I love you.
我要睡觉了
I have to go to sleep now.
等等
Wait.
放松 好的 放松
Easy. Okay, easy.
-等等...  -该死的 你抓稳了
-Wait, wait...  -Hold it steady, damn it.
抓稳了
Hold it steady.
Jack 你在听吗?
Jack, are you there?
把那个递给我
All right, hold that up to me.
-对讲机..递给我  -那手术..
-The walkie..Hold it up to me.  -What about the surgery..
你照做就是了!
Just do it!
是的 Kate 你还好吗?
Yeah, I'm here, Kate. You okay?
是的 我们找到船了
Yeah, I... we've got a boat.
他们让我们走
They're letting us go.
谁让你们走的?
Who's letting you go?
那个金发女人
The blonde woman.
你安全了 你和 Sawyer?
So you're safe, you and Sawyer?
是的
Yes, yeah.
告诉我
Tell me.
告诉你?
Tell you?
坠机的那天 在海滩上..
The first day on the beach,the day of the crash..
我和你将的故事..如果你安全了 告诉我
The story that I told you..If you're safe, tell me.
-你认为这样好吗..  -闭嘴!
-You think this is the best time..  -Shut up!
你... 在给一个小女孩做手术...
You... were doing surgery on a girl...
你搞砸了
and you messed up.
你犯了个错误
You made a mistake.
你撕开了她背部的什么东西
You tore something on her back,
所有的神经都弄碎了...
and all the nerves came loose...
你说你很害怕...
and you said you were so afraid...
那种恐惧是那么的...
and you said the fear was so...
真实 而你又不知道该怎么做...
real, and you didn't know what to do...
所以你数到5...
so you counted to five...
然后你什么都不怕了
and then you weren't afraid anymore...
然后恐惧就不见了
and then it was just gone...
最后你治好了她
and you fixed her.
你救了她
You saved her.
我要你向我许诺 Kate
I need you to make me a promise, Kate.
许诺你再也不要回来找我了
Promise me that you'll never come back here for me.
别回来 Kate
Don't come back, Kate.
Jack 你在哪里...
Jack, where are you...
关掉它
Turn it off.
Jack? Jack 求你了 你在..
Jack? Jack, please, where are..
交易完成了
Trades are comin' up.
我们必须得走了
We gotta go.
-我们走  -好吧
-Let's go.  -Okay.
有些书面文件需要你签字
We have some paperwork that we need you to sign,
随时都可以!
but take your time. There's no rush.
谢谢你!
Thank you.
你能移除那个肿瘤吗?
Were you able to remove the tumor?
是的
Yeah.
你要来做检测 看是不是恶性的
You'll want to do a biopsy,see if it's malignant.
现在我就回我的牢房吗?
So what now, I just go back to my cell?
直到他们想好怎么对付你
Until they figure out what to do with you.
"他们"...
"They"...
他刚才说了什么?
What did he say?
什么?
I'm sorry?
Ben..他说了什么 能让你决定挽救他?
Ben..What did he say that made you want to save his life?
他说的并不重要
It doesn't really matter what he said.
对我来说很重要
It matters to me.
我经历所有的这些
After everything that I have been put through,
你欠我个答案
you owe me an answer.
我只想知道他说了什么?
And I wanna know what he said.
需要纸巾吗?
Tissue?
谢谢
Thank you. Thanks.
我们见过吗?
Have we met?
你好 Burke医生
Hello, Dr. Burke.
-Alpert先生?  -对你丈夫的死我感到很抱歉
-Mr. Alpert?  -I'm, so sorry for your loss.
你在这干吗?
What are you doing here?
我看了新闻
I saw what happened on the news,
办公室的人说你会在这儿
and,your office said you were down here.
我只是想表示我的慰问
I just wanted to express my condolences in person
在我回波特兰之前
before I went back up to Portland.
这是 Ethan 他是我的一个同事
This is Ethan.He's one of my colleagues.
很高兴见到你
It's a pleasure to meet you.
他是被汽车撞死的
He was hit by a bus.
我知道 他们说当时你在场
I know. They say you were there when it happened.
-这不会是...  -不 不 我们面试的时候
-It must have been...  -No, no, in our interview,
我说..我说我想...
I said..I said that I wanted...
让他被汽车撞死
I wanted him to get hit by a bus.
Burke医生 我认为你是过分紧张了
Dr. Burke, I realize you're a little shook up right now,
但这只是一场车祸罢了
but this is just a tragic accident.
你不能责备自己
You can'blame yourself.
我甚至不记得你说过这话
I don't even rember you saying that.
为什么你会在这里 Alpert先生?
Why are you here, Mr. Alpert?
是这样的 uh...
Look, uh...
我知道这不是个好时候
I know the timing is horrible,
但我们对你和
but we came because we're that serious
我们合作的事很认真
about getting you to come work with us.
就6个月
Just give us six months.
如果你想在你妹妹生孩子前回来 那完全不是问题
If you need to, you'll be back before your sister gives birth.
-你怎么知道我的..  -我们是很...
-How did you know that my..  -Well, we're very...
对招募工作很细致
thorough in our recruitment process.
我的妹妹能一起来吗?
Can my sister come?
不行 我们的地方在很远
Won't work. We're pretty remote.
她得不到她所需要的治疗
She wouldn't have access to the treatment that she needs.
但那是在波特兰啊!
But it's Portland.
-那里有很多诊所和..  -实际上
-There's plenty of clinics and..  -Well, actually,
我们的基地不在波特兰
we're not quite in Portland.
我想知道他说了什么
I wanna know what he said.
我在这座岛上三年了 Jack..
I've been on this island for three years, Jack..
3年零2个月加28天
3 years, 2 months and 28 days.
他说如果我...
He said that if I...
让他活下去...
let him live...
我会帮你...
and I helped you...
他将会让我回家
that he would finally let me go home.
本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
双语版字幕由YYeTs春天花花英语教研组制作
仅供学习交流 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
欢迎有能力的爱好者加入我们字幕组 www.YYETS.com
■